[{"answer": " Hi, Evelyn.  Im Ken.  Please have a seat", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Thank you.  Its nice to meet you", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hi, Evelyn.  Im Ken.  Please have a seat", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Likewise.  Now, what can I do for you today", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Thank you.  Its nice to meet you", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "Well, I have a friend who is from India that wants to study here in the U.S", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Likewise.  Now, what can I do for you today", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Well, I have a friend who is from India that wants to study here in the U.S", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Ive been explaining lots of things to him and now hes asking me about th", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 19, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Sure.  I can assist you with calculating the costs.  The first thing we can start wit", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Ive been explaining lots of things to him and now hes asking me about th", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " OK, good", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Sure.  I can assist you with calculating the costs.  The first thing we can start wit", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Depending on the school he chooses, tuition and fees are going to range fro", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 32, "question": " OK, good", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Oh, I see.  Thats a lot of money", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Depending on the school he chooses, tuition and fees are going to range fro", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Yes, school is pretty expensive these days. Books and other study materials ar", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh, I see.  Thats a lot of money", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " All right.  What about all the other expenses besides school costs that th", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Yes, school is pretty expensive these days. Books and other study materials ar", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " We have some national averages for typical living expenses too.  Lets seeroo", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 47, "question": " All right.  What about all the other expenses besides school costs that th", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " OK.  I think this student will probably want an apartment", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 53, "question": " We have some national averages for typical living expenses too.  Lets seeroo", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Sure.  So, depending on which apartment they choose, it will be at least $300 ", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 54, "question": " OK.  I think this student will probably want an apartment", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " They have to eat, right", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Sure.  So, depending on which apartment they choose, it will be at least $300 ", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Yes, of course.  Thats an unavoidable expense.  Other personal costs, includin", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 59, "question": " They have to eat, right", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " It sure is adding up", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Yes, of course.  Thats an unavoidable expense.  Other personal costs, includin", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Thats not all the expenses, yet.  Students have to have health insurance too", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 64, "question": " It sure is adding up", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Wow, thats a lot too", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Thats not all the expenses, yet.  Students have to have health insurance too", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " It is, but medical expenses can run well into the thousands if they dont hav", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Wow, thats a lot too", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Yes, youre right", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 73, "question": " It is, but medical expenses can run well into the thousands if they dont hav", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Other things to think about are whether the student wants a car, whether the", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Yes, youre right", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Do you have the estimates for those costs as well", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Other things to think about are whether the student wants a car, whether the", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I sure do.  A car will cost a student about $4000 a year", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Do you have the estimates for those costs as well", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 83, "question": " I sure do.  A car will cost a student about $4000 a year", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Bringing families really increases expenses too.  Students can calculate an extr", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 84, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " OK, well, Ive got that all written down", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Bringing families really increases expenses too.  Students can calculate an extr", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Great.  With that information, your friend should be able to estimate the cost o", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 89, "question": " OK, well, Ive got that all written down", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Well, thank you.  That was very helpful", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Great.  With that information, your friend should be able to estimate the cost o", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Come back any time if you have more questions", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Well, thank you.  That was very helpful", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " I will.  Bye", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Youre welcome.  Come back any time if you have more questions", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Take care", "docId": "06-03", "aSentId": 96, "question": " I will.  Bye", "qSentId": 95}]
